thebestsingapore.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy | The Best Singapore

The Best Singapore Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. References in this document to “us,” “our,” and “we” refer to The Best Singapore.

 **What information do we collect?**  
When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your Name, Email address or other details to help you with your experience.

We never ask for personal or private information.

 **When do we collect information?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site.

 **How do we use your information?**  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

– To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

– To send periodic newsletter emails.

 **Google Cookies  
**We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 **Third Party Disclosure**  
The information we collect is used to improve the content of this site and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes. That being said, your information could be shared under the following circumstances:

– We use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, these third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with those business activities.

– As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions.

– We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.

– If it becomes necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.

 **Third Party Links**  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our site to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including sites which have a link on our site, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

 **Your Consent**  
By using this site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
